letsget.net 2010-12-17

# LetsGet.Net

PRIVACY POLICY

At Kimberg, LLC and LetsGet.Net (hereinafter collectively referred to as “LetsGet”), protecting the privacy of customers and clients is of great importance. This Privacy Policy explains the type of personal information LetsGet collects, how LetsGet uses and discloses that information, and how LetsGet protects that personal information. 

1\. Customers and Merchants. 

LetsGet collects certain personal information about Merchants and customers. 

“Merchants” are businesses and business owners that engage LetsGet to provide web-based remote ordering services. 

“Customers” are individuals that place orders from LetsGet Merchants through the LetsGet system. 

“Personal information” is any information that identifies or may identify a user as a specific individual, including but not limited to, name, address, zip code, phone number and email address, as well as financial information, including order history, payment, and credit card information. 

2\. Use and Disclosure of Personal Information.  LetsGet will not disclose any personal information about any Customer or Merchant to any person or entity except (i) LetsGet will share personal information about a Customer with the Merchant from whom the customer places an order, (ii) LetsGet may provide personal information to its vendors and suppliers when necessary , and (iii) LetsGet may release personal information to comply with law, enforce or apply the terms of any of user agreement, or to protect the rights, property or safety of LetsGet, Customers and Merchants, or others. Please note that LetsGet is not responsible for how its Merchants use any Customer’s personal information. Please refer to the Merchant’s privacy policy for information as to how our Merchants use Customer personal information. LetsGet does not grant access to Merchants of any Customer's full credit card information. 

3\. Safeguards.  The security of personal information is very important to LetsGet. LetsGet combines industry-standard technical safeguards with an employee code of conduct and training to help ensure the integrity and privacy of personal information. Only authorized LetsGet employees, agents or independent contractors are permitted to access personal information, and all such employees, agents or independent contractors must agree in writing to abide by the Privacy Policy. 

4\. Cookies and Personal Information.  Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of LetsGet’s coolest features, and we recommend that you leave them turned on. Customers and Merchants may always contact LetsGet to (i) delete their personal information from LetsGet’s systems; (ii) update their personal information; or (iii) change their preferences with respect to marketing contacts, by emailing LetsGet at privacy@letsget.net. 

5\. Subordination of LetsGet Privacy Policy.  Upon written notice from Merchant, LetsGet will accept and enforce the privacy policies of the Merchant in any area where the Merchant’s privacy policy is preferred over LetsGet’s Privacy Policy.
